# RACHNA SHAH

# SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

9769218669

rachnashah279@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/rachna-shahba5110142

A/4,Neet & Geet,Santacruz (W),Mumbai-54

## SKILLS

- C#
- .NET
- MS SQL and Oracle DB
- JavaScript
- HTML and CSS
- JAVA
- · Good communication skills
- · Quick learner

# CERTIFICATE / AWARD

- MicroSoft Azure AZ-209 Certification and Training
- Star Performer of the quarter 2023 reward and Pat on Back Award from Capgemini.
- Training and Certification for SAFE Agilist 4.6 and 5
- POB (Pat On Back) Award from LTI -NETS for good performance in 2020.
- .NET MVC and Agile Training

# EDUCATION

- BTECH (Electronics Engineering): 4.8 / 6 GPA
  SNDT University (2013-2017)
- HSC (Mumbai University): 66%
- SSC (Maharashtra Sate Board): 82.36%

#### PROFILE

Currently working in Capgemini with 5.2 years of experience. I have ability to learn new technologies with good grasping skills. Striving for a position where I can make maximum use of my knowledge and contribute towards the growth of the company.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Capgemini

Concerto - AXA Assistance

September 2021-Present

- Concerto is an application used by AXA Assistance coordinators/agents to provide all kinds of assistance to their customers. The main business line for France is Automobile and Home assistance.
- CMS batch is used to create and validate the cases created by Salesforce and save it in Concerto database, as the front office of this application was taken over by eCare team.
- Developed and handled testing of the CMS batch and API to create cases.
- TOOLS & TECHNOLOGY: C#, API, XML, PostMan, MS SQL, Azure and GIT

# **Larsen & Toubro Infotech**

3DS Portal - NETS

April 2021-September 2021

- 3DS application is used to display data of 3D secure transaction to banks.
- .Net Core based application. Agile methodology is followed.
- TOOLS & TECHNOLOGY: .NET CORE, Angular,SQL, Visual Studio ,VS Code, Angular,GIT and TFS.

# Kossu - NETS

May 2019-April 2021

- Kossu is an card blocking application in Finland. Kossu DB was used with other application to share card holder information.
- · Handled testing and development singlehanded.
- TOOLS & TECHNOLOGY: Oracle DB, Oracle APEX, Eclipse, JAVA, SOAP UI, XML,SVN and Jira

## Fraud Portal - NETS

July 2018-April 2021

- FraudPortal is used in Nordicsto create cases for fraudulent transactions.
- Banksand Merchants uses this application to handle fraud cases.
- SAFE and AGILE methodology used with PI planning ever 2 month.
- Handleddevelopment ,testing and RnD task related to EpiServer upgrade.
- TOOLS & TECHNOLOGY: C#,ADO.NET,EPISERVER, HTML,CSS,AJAX, jQuery, JS,MS SQL,JIRA and SVN